

# **LUKASZ AUGUSTYN**

## **SKILLS**

HTML
CSS
English B2
WordPress
WooCommerce
RWD
PhotoShop & Illustrator
JavaScript
Git
SEO
C# & Unity

Teamwork
Planning
Independence
Punctuality
Communicativeness
Driving License - B

# **CONTACT DETAILS**

Łukasz Augustyn Apollina 1/24 80-180 Kowale (Gdańsk) 10.03.1990

**513 249 535** 

uki.gd@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT**

Building websites and online stores has been my hobby for several years. I am looking for orders in this direction to constantly develop as a web developer.

The jobs he gets are usually from small companies or private individuals. Most often I use WordPress to build a website so that the client can also manage it in some way. Below are some links to websites where I participated in the construction:

grawerjulia.pl osrodekprzywydmach.pl wysepka.pl

All pages were made on WordPress / WooCommerce.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

01.2019 - NOW
SERVICE OF ALARMS, CAMERAS AND HELPDESK
Service and service coordinator

**01.2017 - 01.2019 SERVICE OF PHONES AND COMPUTERS**Independent service technician

01.2014 - 01.2017
ONLINE SHOP
Managing the website and online store

### **EDUCATION**

Profesja Szkoły Policealne w Gdańsku 10.2011 - 06.2013

Faculty: IT technician

Major: Computer Science with a Technical Diploma

Szkoły Elektryczne i Elektroniczne w Gdańsku 09.2006 - 05.2011

**Faculty: Electronics Technician** 

**Major: Electronics** 

#### INTERESTED

Mountain and bicycle trips Playing football



I consent to the processing of my personal data contained in my job application for the purposes necessary for recruitment in accordance with the Act of August 29, 1997 on the Protection of Personal Data (Journal of Laws No. 133, item 883).